yes cold calling sucks it's challenging
and that's exactly why it works so well
if you're doing practices from 1972 well
you're probably not going to see the
results you want on today's episode
however we're going to tell you exactly
why cold calling sucks and why cold
calling does work so well it's because
it sucks man this is good check it
[Music]
out hey hey hey everyone welcome to
another great episode of the sales
evangelist podcast I'm your host Donald
C
Kelly the sales evangelist and I'm so
excited for another great episode I'm so
excited to be here with you today and on
this episode I have the one and only
Nick and Arman on the podcast they're
both the uh the hosts over at 30 minutes
to president club and they just wrote an
amazing book All Around cold calling
they break things down tactically they
have they have sound bites with QR codes
you just scan the QR codes in a book and
go listen to the sound bites with the
tactics and the strategies they're
sharing it's very actionable and when I
got them on this episode you're going
hear how they just kept going back and
back and back and back and back and
forth with just so many great insights
breaking down code call some of the
mistakes that we're making why it's
challenging for most sales reps and what
you can use what you should be doing in
order to be successful with your code
call so if you're looking to improve
your code calling game this is a must
and I want you to go ahead and save it
you can also check out their podcast 30
minutes president club we have details
down in the show notes and access to
their books if this is your first time
listening to our show we want to make
sure that you leave with some insights
to help you build top of funnel as well
as help you to improve your clothes rate
as we dive in today listen to some of
these principles see how you can apply
them in your sales efforts and don't
just listen and pass it on like and move
on to the next one just listen go back
again and take the principles and
actually apply them I know you're going
to see great success check it
out Arman Nick pleasure to have you guys
here we made it the one and only Donald
Kelly it's a pleasure to be here with
you shoot man well I'm excited guys are
a pretty dope podcast I chat about that
for a little bit and we're going to we
put a link down below so folks can get
access to it um and and all the fun
stuff you guys are doing with that and
how long you guys been podcasting now
it's been like what four or five years
Al together gosh we started in in 2020
but Arman and I have known each other
for a very very long time we've we've
started a couple businesses together
some that have done well some that have
taught us a lot uh and that's the price
of tuition but um a lot of it informs
the the stuff that we talk about and and
teach uh and believe about selling
today and I think that's what makes it
so unique cuz not only with your
business you were you actually did the
stuff as contributors as well as Leaders
plus with the content you've developed
and you have a premise that you came up
with that led to the creation of a book
right yeah it is so we have a book
coming out called cold calling sucks and
that's why it works and the whole sort
of philosophy around it is we we
actually pulled some data on like we're
trying to figure out we wanted to write
a book on cold calling cuz arm and I
have both had a lot of experience cold
calling and it's been meaningful for us
but before you write a book on cold
calling you got to figure out like is it
actually effective or was this just like
an experience that he and I had in Niche
spaces and so we actually partnered with
gong and we pulled data from 300 million
cold calls and what we saw was for the
50th percentile seller it's actually not
very good they make something like 800
dials they talk to like 43 people their
connect rate isn't great and they end up
booking like two meetings off of 800
which is basically calling every single
day for a month straight but the best
sales people actually not even the best
the the top cortile salespeople they
make those same 800 dials they actually
connect with double the number of
prospects because they do things like
they call their numbers they're a bit
more strategic about how they're dialing
and they end up booking something like
18 or 19 meetings off of the same number
of dials and that's crazy 18 or 19 over
two that's like a huge difference
correct correct and so the reality is no
matter how good you get at cold calling
it's going to be painful and
uncomfortable and awkward you're going
to deal with rude prospects and
Gatekeepers that shut you down and
you're going to hit voicemail a lot but
for an hour of work a day there's pretty
much no other way to generate real
pipeline results like that than cold
calling and so the premise of the book
is hey no matter what it's going to suck
but that's actually why it works because
so many people never get to that top
75th percentile
because they give up because of how
challenging it is and if it seems like
wow that's kind of hard though to get to
the top 75th percentile the other thing
to realize Donald is the bar is set very
very low and so to get good really just
requires you to get a couple things
right which hopefully we can share some
examples today of like some of the ways
you can set yourself apart from the
average
telemarketer dang this is good well if
you're just listening to this episode I
mean you got the cost of the mission is
already there you already got so many
good insight already that's going to
help you but specifically we want to get
into some of these things um there there
a few things that we started talking
about um one was the opener two the
objection and then three you have a
really unique idea on the value
proposition so let's let's dive into
both all three of those and just take
one at a time we can break them down I'm
talking about the opener right now
because you gave us some idea and about
the connect rate and I'm sure in a book
again giv a lot more ideas on how we can
do that better but specifically with the
opener so many people get Frozen at that
point it's kind of like a dog chasing a
car right they you know what do you do
when you actually catch the car how do
we do how do we open this thing
right I've been making $800 and I got
somebody like H what what works what
what should I be thinking about yeah
it's funny when you almost get surprised
when someone picks up the phone
and I think the unfortunate reality
Donald is what most salespeople do is
they greet people on a cold call the
same way that they greet all of these
other people in their life which is hey
how's your day going or hey did I catch
you at a bad time and the problem is
when you lead with an opener like hey
it's Arman from Northwestern how's your
day going the prospect knows that you're
a stranger and they know that you don't
actually care how their day is going so
you'll be met with an exasperated sigh
that sounds
like fine how can I help you and that's
code word for I know you're a
salesperson what are you trying to sell
me the other often often times thing
that will happen is people say did I
catch you had a bad time which it's
always a bad time it's a cold call I've
literally heard people say yes it's a
bad time hang up block your number and
now you never get to see that Prospect
again and on top of that it puts you in
a position of inferiority those are the
traditional bad canned cold cold call
openers but Donald there are some better
canned cold call openers that I still
don't think are great another good
example is the permission based opener
which is Donald I know you weren't
expecting my call 30 seconds to tell you
why I called and then you can tell me
whether or not it's fit that worked
really really well a couple years ago
the problem is everyone's using that one
now too and so they're getting lumped in
with the telemarketers as well and so
what Nick and I have resolved to do is
the only way that you can truly break
the telemarketer perception is to pick
up the phone and lead with an opener
that cannot be canned and the only thing
that cannot be canned is if I lead with
something about you so you want to lead
with context so the first opener that
I'll give you is What's called the heard
the name tossed around opener and it
sounds like this I know if I was calling
you what I want to do is I want to take
someone you respect an industry peer
maybe a competitor or maybe someone that
you've done business with before maybe
we share a mutual investor and I'm going
to lead with that up front so I might
say hey Donald we work with a few other
sales podcasts out there folks like a 30
minutes to president Club it's Arman
from podcast Inc have you heard her name
tossed around what I'm doing is I know
you run the sales evangelist podcast and
so I'm going to name an industry peer
the 30 minutes to president's Club
podcast and if you know they work with
the guys at 30 MPC you're going to be
like even if you haven't heard of
podcast Inc you're going to be like no
but I'm not going to on you because
I know you guys work with Arman and Nick
I guess what what's this call about so
when you lead with context about how you
know appear in their space you
completely change the tenor and the
demeanor of the call within the first 5
Seconds
yeah and I think one of the cool part
about that is and and go back to human
psychology to what I've seen over the
years it's like not over the years I
mean I've only been around for like 40
years not 2,000 about 10,000 but that
you know human behavior often times go
back to people are more friendly to
folks who are like them right or might
see it from the same camp um it's like
if you travel abroad and all of a sudden
you see another American could be
somebody from the backwoods of
Appalachia that I never talked to but
the fact that you have American is like
oh yeah hey man how you doing doing um
but I I I I like that because it it
gives me this I think it sets the stage
you're not a a foe what's up and I think
this leads into the next component well
and the other thing here Donald is you
called it out like people they're going
to be more friendly to people that are
like them or people that know people
like them and the difference between and
so actually a lot of sales people try to
accomplish that with the how's your day
going or did I catch you at a bad time
they use this like these false
pleasantries or they try to build
Rapport at the interruption well that's
just like acting like you care about the
other person or you're in their Network
Arman is actually showing it with that
her the name TOS own opener hey you know
we work with a couple other podcasts
like you and so the data supported this
also we pulled some data with gong uh
did I catch you had a bad time had a 2%
success rate on cold calls how's your
day going was a little better and it was
like a 7% success rate the opener that
Armand just used had an 11 half% success
rate which if you think about a career
of cold calling is a Prett dramatic
difference um not only because it gets
you to the part where you can give your
pitch but also because if you think
about the tenor of the call even if you
get to the part of your pitch on hey did
I catch you at a bad time they're
already looking at you as this like
subservient telemarket type versus
they're actually going to be hearing out
your pitch if they're like okay wait
this person works with peers of mine or
they they work with other companies who
we share the same investor and so if you
think about the downstream impact of
showing them that context rather than
acting like you're a really friendly
Rapport building seller like big
difference yeah you know the other part
that I like about that um you know the
notion back there again it also helps me
to recognize that you're not like this
uh um it's not like a guinea pig or
you're not uh I don't want to make it
like a novice in a sense and I know yeah
they're going to have new people out
there but I don't want I want to deal
with somebody that can actually solve my
problem that have relevant you know a
relevant problem that I have than
somebody who's just going to um you know
is a is a seller just trying to just
book an appointment um I I'll be more
upt to talk to somebody that I feel um
has that industry backing or industry
experti that's right so so another
opener that you can use Donald if you
don't want to use the her the name
tossed around opener is a variant of
that permission based opener which is
can that I call the tailored permission
opener and all you're going to do is
you're going to take your your normal
permission based opener and you're going
to lead with the thing that made you
call them in the first place uh the
piece of research that you found about
them so that might sound something like
Emma I just finished reading your press
release about the new office opening in
Tacoma and I'm going to be honest this
is a cold call but it is a well
researched one and I'm wondering if I
can get half a minute to share why that
press release had prompted me to call
you and then you can totally hang up on
me if it doesn't make sense from there
what I'm doing is the key is that office
opening in Tacoma needs to be something
that I can relate to what my product
helps with so when I was selling billing
software to law firms I would look for
things like if they had just opened a
new office which would have tax
implications or if they had just won a
big case which would usually mean they
were collecting money which our software
could help with or if they had just
opened a new Practice Group at the law
firm which often led to billing
complexity we could help with and so
what I recommend sellers do is look for
their like top five things that they
could be their go-to that they can
easily find about their prospects but
then they can relate to what they help
with and so this one like tells them hey
this is a cold call but it's a Well
researched one and not only am I telling
them that I'm showing them that by
having that context of what I found be
the first thing that comes out of my
mouth I just finished reading about your
office opening even before I say my name
so here's the other part to that too and
and I know this is one is a one that
comes up all the time with sales reps
and sales leaders always push back on it
you mentioned like the research aspect
of it how important is that in this era
of cold cold Outreach and then to what
level because it doesn't sound like it
was like you're not doing a you know a
thesis uh you know a doctorate here but
you're you are doing some kind of you
Gathering some kind of information not
sound like a buffoon when you do the
call talk to us about that I don't want
to sound like a buffoon so there's a
spectrum and any either extreme on that
spectrum is wrong the wrong thing to do
is to your point point do a deep dive
thesis research where I'm reading
arman's entire biography listening to
every podcast he ever been on and
spending 15 hours or frankly even like a
good hour plus researching somebody who
like I might call them and they're a
total jerk or they just bought a
competitor or like their numers bad or
I've had this before someone is's now
deceased and I spent all this time
reading their bio so over researching is
not the right way to do things the other
end of the spectrum would be zero
research and that's actually a bit less
because of like how you're going to
engage on the call because I think
sometimes people over rotate on
personalization rather than relevance
the thing is and this goes back to what
we talked about in the beginning about
that gong data doing a little bit of
prep to make sure you're calling the
right people at the right time with the
right trigger will Jack your meeting
booked rate and frankly even your
connect rate up really really high so if
you think about that Spectrum our
recommendation is find the top five
triggers that would make you believe
someone could be a good customer and
when you're doing your research
intentionally look for those five
triggers in order and when you find one
that's your reason for calling them you
don't need to keep researching and so
you can start to operationalize this
stuff and become far more efficient just
to add on to that you know how in
football they have this thing called the
two-minute drill which is you have two
minutes to score I break that down into
the one minute drill which is you have
one minute to decide if you want to work
the account and also find one thing that
you can use in your opener and the
moment you find one of them stop so it
should only take you 30 seconds to
figure out if you want to work in
account or not so you should know can
you work inter a national accounts can
you work accounts under this many
employees can you work accounts over
this many employees you have a list of
10 things that disqualify an account you
go Bop you hit them back to back to back
to back to back to back to back 10
things 30 seconds boom you decide to
work the account awesome now you have
your top five list one two 3 four five
the first one you find stop it should
take you 30 seconds to disqualify 30
seconds to research find one thing
that's what you put in your opener you
know and what I what I what I've seen is
on the other side is um where the
sellers will literally take they jump
back and forth because what I'm hearing
from what you're sharing here is
obviously your industry expertise or
your your your Niche expertise right
you're not doing like 15 different types
of accounts you're only focusing on your
your one type of account going through
that which I think obviously makes total
load of sense I love this man this is
great now I got my opener down um we
went ahead and did some examples there
um but now I'm I've got an objection
like I'm getting you're going to get
those um and some people climb up when
they get the objection what are some of
your thoughts and objection Aman we
talked a little bit about this at the
beginning um why don't you to lead off
with that yeah so first thing is a lot
of people think they need to handle the
objections they need to fight the
objection so Donald for example if you
say I'm I'm using a competitor we're
we're recording this currently on
Riverside FM let's say that I'm calling
from some other recording platform I'm
calling you from Zoom the moment you say
ah we use Riverside try to handle the
objection they try to say all the
different reasons why Zoom is better
than
Riverside but the problem is Donald
you're not actually thinking about the
tradeoffs of whether or not zoom is
better when you give me that objection
you're just throwing the first thing
that you can think of to say I don't
want to hear the sales pitch I've got
something I don't have time for this
right now I'm on Riverside peace and so
you're not even logical reasoning yet
and the reason for that is most
objections are not objections to the
solution they're objections to the cold
call itself they're reactions to the
interruption and so you're just going to
Chuck the first chair you can find at
the room to get me out of the room as
quickly as possible and so in order to
wake up your brain and take you from
reacting to listening the first thing I
need to do when you give me an objection
is I need to agree with the objection so
Donald let's just pretend that you give
me that objection now we're using
Riverside Inc yeah I'm going to say hey
Donald I I totally get that you know
honestly I should have assumed that you
were using a great platform your guys'
separate audio tracks They sound really
really good already and you're probably
not going to
switch hey just so no one from my team
cold calls you again
could you give me a sense of is it that
and at that point I'm going to ask you a
question that gets you talking more
about your solution and so for example
if I was using Riverside Inc one of the
things I don't like or that I that I
that I'll usually point at is I'll say
hey just so I know that it makes sense
for no one else to call you could you
give me a sense I imagine you have some
cold call scripts that you've wanted to
screen share in the past how have you
guys gone about doing that in the past
and I can hit you with a trap question
now that gets you to think about what
other Solutions might be out there but I
can't do that until I agree with the
objection and I incentivize you to give
me a little bit more information by
saying hey just know team cold calls you
again could you really help me
understand why it doesn't make sense for
us to call you again the the piece that
Armand added about the the agreeing and
the incentivizing is really really
important because what your average
salesperson does when they get that
objection is they fast forward or they
or they jump right to that trap question
that Armand asked they go right to okay
how can I beat this competitor or how
can I get this person to tell me about
something they can't do so I can beat
the competitor the problem is that's
what most telemarketers do when they get
resistance from their Prospect they turn
up the sales pressure and that that only
makes your prospect less willing to hear
you out or engage you because you're
putting yourself in telemarket or Camp
your prospect they didn't ask to be cold
you're interrupting them and now they
told you a reason that had some
legitimacy for why they wouldn't want to
meet with you and now you're pushing
even harder and that's where I think a
lot of sales people lose the the EQ that
often makes them good sales people and
why they got into sales in the first
place is what arman's doing is
acknowledging like okay wait a second I
interrupted this person they just told
me they're on a competitor they're
getting the job done today yeah this
one's totally my bad you probably would
have called me if you had been
interested in our solution or I should
have assumed you'd have something in
place you're a really popular podcast
and when you do that it brings the sales
pressure down and again they start to
see you as a professional they start to
see you as a peer you're not someone
who's going to just try to Ram their
product no matter what
I think when when I when I we did a
little survey and one of the things we
found like what most people say with
salespeople is that they feel like this
it's almost like a confrontation um that
they get with a seller because the
seller if give the seller I'm not
interested it's automatically the seller
feel like you're insulted their family
line and it's like you I I have to show
my my my loyalty to my to my my role and
fight back with you but what I you
almost like from what you're sharing
there Nick it was almost I can see and I
can feel the confrontation if I do go to
that question that it's a battle and
you're not going to win you're not ever
going to win that's where the hangup
comes but I would love what you go back
to what you said I'm on like for me when
you brought that up now I started to
think like it doesn't matter it's like
it's a cognitive thing cuz that's my
world right now it's podcasting and
you're bringing up this question that
makes me want to show my level of
superiority as an expert and I'm going
to answer that question now but you just
made it a conversation and I'm like holy
holy moly this guy from the opener is
somebody that I do have affiliation with
and somehow and he sounds normal so
maybe I should have a conversation and
he asked a intriguing question you know
what I mean I making sense there if
there's one thing to that point uh
Donald that I think sellers should
practice when they're handling
objections is just the moment you get an
objection practice laughing and agreeing
with the objection and that that alone
exactly there you are that alone it
shows that you're comfortable when most
sellers get hit with with not interest
that they're like they start to Stam or
stutter and it comes off like they're a
telemarketer versus when you laugh and
agree it's like oh I guess this one's
really not a fit if you say no budget
I'm going to be like totally get it man
look honestly it sucks to buy software
today like nowadays it's hard enough to
keep something let alone it is to buy
something new in your head you're like
oh my God finally someone's not going to
try to sell me and now we can have an
actual conversation you can do that
basic Bas with any objection in the
world I mean there's so much more to
this and I know in the book it go deeper
but the cool thing the question that
comes with that is like how do you get a
seller to that point because you guys
have been doing it for a minute is that
more of like the the practice before you
make the calls what's your theory your
thoughts on that
side or just make mess up so so if we're
going to talk about objections solely
here the first is recognizing what Arman
called out earlier which is when you you
get an objection more often than not it
has nothing to do with what you're
selling or for like your cause it has
everything to do with the interruption
you picked up the phone and it might
have been a good time for you and this
might be your job to make cold calls but
for your prospect it is an entirely
unwelcome Interruption to their day and
that's okay our job is to start
conversations with new prospects but the
first thing to recognize is they're just
trying to get you off the phone they
don't want to talk to a
telemarketer and so when you realize
that you'll see first your chances of
success are higher when you take this
approach rather than trying to fight the
objection immediately but second to your
point Donald of like how does somebody
actually get good at this yeah the key
is practicing and if I go back to that
data that I talked about earlier average
cold caller makes 800 cold calls calling
every single that's like calling every
day for an hour for an entire month they
talk to 43 people if you think about the
amount of OB ection handling practice
they get off of 43 cold calls over a
month like that's not enough to get
really really good but if I go for a
walk around my neighborhood for 30
minutes and I just practice that
agreeing and laugh agree and laugh or if
I'm trying to get good at my opener I
say my opener again and again and again
and again and again I can get a
quarter's worth of cold calling practice
in in a half hour walk and I can get
some sunshine and I can get some some
steps in and I'm a generally happy
person happier person and I'm a better
seller and so the key is isolate some of
your core talk tracks the opener you're
going to use the pitch that you're going
to use your agree and laugh in response
to objections and if you can get those
components right you can get to that
75th percentile pretty quickly because
almost every single cold call has an
opener has a pitch and has an objection
that you're going to need to respond to
dope love it the last opponent you have
a strong staunch feeling relationship on
this word um the value prop uh
um who wants to take this one because
now I as a seller I got an opener I know
how to handle objection but I got to say
something to grab this person's
attention um when it comes to what I
could do for
them what about the value prop that we
need to be aware
of so Donald I have a question for you
oh snap
if I were to run a Dum Dum lollipop
under the sink water and drop it on a
shag rug and give it to you would you
eat it no man it's disgusting why what
what does it look like it's nasty it's
dirty it's has hair like hair hang
exactly you can see the hair coming off
of this thing and so I immediately
created a picture of a problem and an
emotional visceral reaction out of you
and I did that by doing things like
explaining the scenery giving you idea
of specific objects or things where it's
like here's the dumb dumb lollipop under
the water with the shag rug I'm telling
you the story of the trigger problem to
create a visceral
reaction and then if I told you well
here you go man I have a clearly rap Dum
Dum lollipop and I knew you really
wanted one You' take the damn lollipop
because now the solution has context
right the problem is most most sellers
lead with solutions that mean absolutely
nothing to a prospect whatsoever they'll
say things like my solution is a single
source of Truth an all-in-one platform a
single pane of glass number one
everyone's using those things which
immediately recategorized you as a
telemarketer but then number two don't
actually mean anything to a prospect no
one knows what a single source of Truth
for compensation management the only way
that you can actually get a prospect who
listen listen to a pitch given how
desensitized they are to these pitches
is to pinpoint a problem or talk about a
problem so specifically in their day
that literally they get triggered by it
and they sit up so for example we're on
this platform Riverside here again our
favorite podcast recording platform for
those of you listening you might not be
familiar with this problem when you
start clicking record on Riverside it
starts recording on separate video and
audio tracks local to your hard drive
what that means is it prioritizes the
download on your computer over your
connection with the different people on
the call and what happens is everyone's
face gets really really grainy so it
looks like we're talking to each other
in a 1993 movie before they had
HDTVs and so if I lead with that Donald
and I say like typically when I'm
talking to people who are using
Riverside they love a lot of the fact
that it can record on separate audio
tracks but they can't stand it when they
literally can't see their host facial
expressions anymore because they look
like a movie from 19 72 that gets you to
sit up and you might even laugh a little
because you're like holy that guy
knows my business and then all I have to
do Donald is I need to say one sentence
that makes the problem go away so I
might say pass recording platform Inc
records both in the cloud but then also
to your devices at the same time so you
never have to deal with podcast
graininess again I don't even need to
explain much about my solution if I nail
the triggering problem correct first and
then I'm just going to ask you Donald
are you open to learning more that's a
problem prop over a value
prop dang come on man it's just like I
love it I love it I love it so here's
the other part to that that I I find is
really fascinating um the the problem
prop um is the is the is going back to
this the the studies that show that 60
to I think it's 65 to 70 about 65% of
human population are visual people and
we know from like you know if you're
speaking from stage or whatnot the
storytelling Act aspect where you just
put in your head everything you say one
I visualized it but then it go back to
what you're you're verifying it makes me
um since it's like a storytelling mode
it makes me docile so to speak because
now I'm listening to everything that
you're saying and like you verified it
does put you in this different esant
where I do see you as this expert and
you do understand that problem
oftentimes I find that people who
understand a problem better than me I
will relinquish um my time to them
because I feel they're not like you said
that's subservient they're bringing
something to me that I don't know um and
it's a strategy that I found to be very
effective in so many different walks of
life when you can come as tell me about
a problem better than I can articulate
it then icipher that you are going to be
more of an expert at it than me you know
making sense there 100% the if you can
describe the problem in extremely
dangerous specificity not only does it
get them to sit up there's no way you
could be a complete random
by being able to describe the problem
that well when you're able to describe a
problem their situation so specifically
so accurately it shows that you get
their business and that's the best way
to get them to listen to you is you
establish your credibility as a peer by
showing them that you understand what it
looks like to live in their shoes not
understand what it looks like to
copypaste your product marketer pitch
language no offense to your product
marketing people RPM like you know trth
well this is great I mean I want to go
back to you know just wrap all this
stuff up all this stuff can be found in
your book um can you talk to us a little
bit more about this why you guys decided
to write a book right now and then how
we can get a hold of
that what's funny is there are so many
sellers today who are going through a
second phase of transition where the
first phase of transition was I can send
a million emails a mile using all these
automated sequences and now the problem
is everyone can do that literally a
prospect's inbox is flooded with 10,000
emails every single day people actually
rotate email inboxes where they send 25
emails per day out of 20 different
inboxes because you literally get spam
blocked if you send any more than that
so the bar for email has gotten so so so
low because it's so easy for everyone to
do it and so you see a lot of these
teams that are like shoot the only way I
can get out in front of all these other
sellers is by picking up the phone and
folks there is an awesome opportunity
right now where the average cold caller
today still really really sucks
especially because all they've been
doing is sending cold emails and so we
broke down every single step of the cold
call step by step throughout our book
cold calling sucks and that's why it
works tracks for every single step of
the cold call and there are even QR
codes sprinkled throughout the book that
that contain voiceovers so you can
literally hear the tone throughout the
book so you know exactly how you should
sound as well and so if you want to go
check it out folks you can go get that
at 30 mc.com
backbook done we'll put that in our show
notes and amazing podcast you guys have
too so we have a link down in the show
notes so folks can get access to that as
well um appreciate you guys coming on
the show today giving us some good
wisdom give us some good guidance we
understand how to do our openers we know
how to do an objection and then we
understand that we need to drop the
value and go for problems so appreciate
you guys man thanks so much for coming
on the show today thank you for having
us it's a lot of fun
that was Nick and Arman both of them
have been highly successful in their
sales career not only as individual
contributors but also as sales leaders
and also as guides helping you and me to
be able to learn how we can improve our
game the book is fabulous and I highly
recommend you check it out there's a
link down in the show notes and you can
also check out their podcast 30 minutes
to president Club I want you to thrive
and succeed I want to help you as much
as possible and that's why we bring on
guests like this who have amazing
insights strategies tactical things that
you can use apply them and tell us how
you how it worked for you you can find
us on LinkedIn also you can go to the
sales evangelist. learn about some of
our upcoming training programs as well
as our communities as always I want you
to thrive I want you to succeed I want
you to go out raise your level of
thinking do big things and make some
money in the process see you on the next
one
[Music]